# Hyecheol (Jerry) Jang

□ (+1) 608-770-1154 | Myecheol.jang@wisc.edu | Ohyecheol123 (GitHub) | Ohyecheol (LinkedIn)

# Summary.

Interested in finding optimized solution using Cloud (MS Azure) and writing understandable codes. Passionate about new technolgies/languages/solutions. Experienced in backend/frontend development, deployment/operation, and project management. Open to internship opportunities as a software developer or solution architect. Expect to graduate in Dec, 2023.

### **Education**

#### **University of Wisconsin-Madison**

Madison, WI, United States

Jul. 2018 - Current

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE; DOUBLE MAJOR IN STATISTICS; MINOR IN ENTREPRENEURSHIP • Dean's List: Fa18, Sp19, Sp20 | **GPA: 3.89/4.00** 

- Director of Technology at Korean American Scientist Association Wisconsin Chapter: Developed/Maintained NPO Chapter website and other useful IT tools for chapter management; responsible for various marketing, network activities, leadership board, and decision making.
- · Library Technology Student Assistant at College Library, Memorial Library, and CALS Computing Lab

# Proiects\_

#### **KSEA-Wisconsin Event Ticket System**

Madison, WI, United States

PROJECT MANAGER & BACK-END DEVELOPER

- Building automated event ticket generation / admission service for the NPO | Est. Release: Nov. 2022
- · Automatically send QR code with ticket information to the event participants, check ticket validity and todos during admission with officers' mobile device
- · Using Azure Function, Azure Blob Storage (for static website hosting), Azure Cosmos DB, CloudFlare (CDN) to minimize bandwidth, React Native

#### BusanDevelopers Event Calendar https://github.com/BusanDevelopers/BGM-Event-Calendar-API

Busan, South Korea

PROJECT MANAGER & FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

https://github.com/BusanDevelopers/BGM-Event-Calendar-Webpage

Jan 2022

- Successfully built web event calendar for devleopers community | Led project, Collaborated with one back-end developer and one front-end developer
- Used React (MUI), NodeJS, Azure Cosmos DB, ExpressJS, and ReDoc | Manually set TypeScript React environment using ESLint, Prettier, WebPack, and Babel
- Effectively divided the project into smaller milestones, manage teammates' performance, and conduct weekly meetings

## KSEA-Wisconsin Website Rebuilding Project https://github.com/KSEAWisconsin/kseawisconsin.github.io

Madison, WI, United States

Nov. 2019

PROJECT MANAGER & DEVELOPER

- Built website for NPO Chapter | Led project, Collaborated with five developers | Used HTML, CSS, Jekyll, Git, Jira, MS Teams, Adobe XD
- · Divided tasks for collaboration accordingly | Provided training resources and counter errors and problems during the development process
- Successfully minimized operation budget GitHub Pages to host; used CloudFlare (CDN) to minimize bandwidth and yaml file database for easier modification
- V2 project now launched (Est. Release: Dec. 2022) Add admin portal (Web-based GUI), elegant design, Next.JS-powered website, Serve on MS Azure

# CloudFlare Public Dynamic IP Update Script https://github.com/hyecheol123/Cloudflare-Public-Dynamic-IP-Update

Madison, WI, United States

Aug. 2019

• Built a script to update server's dynamic ip address to CloudFlare (DDNS) | Used Bash Shell Script | 50+ GitHub Star

# Work Experience \_

DEVELOPER

uniQon Seoul, South Korea Apr. 2020 - Oct. 2020 TECHNICAL LEAD

- Used NodeJS (TypeScript) and MongoDB to develop and operate API server, web page, and admin portal • Elaborated idea and developed products that provide "real" college application data and mentor information to prospective applicants with their high school
- · Closely collaborated with CEO to build concrete business plans | Trained Interns/Software Developers and engage in HR tasks
- · Implemented IT infrastructure and remote working environment with Microsoft Teams, Jira, and GitHub

information, keywords from extracurricular activities, and target school lists and majors

· Adopt Agile software development workflow (Scrum) with weekly feedback to team/individuals | Traveled frequently for business meetings and recruiting

**Republic of Korea Army** Busan, South Korea

SOCIAL SERVICE AGENT (SOCIAL WELFARE)

Oct. 2020 - Jul. 2022

· Served at Wonkwang Nursing Home (Long-Term Care Facilities) to complete mendatory military duty of South Korea

### Honors & Awards \_

#### AI·Blockchain Idea Pitching Competition (Third Edition)

Busan, South Korea

Presentation: Bird Strike Prevention Methods at Gadeokdo New Airport Using Big Data and Machine Learning

Aug. 2022

# Skills

**Programming Language**: TypeScript, JavaScript, Java, SQL, R, C, Python, Bash

Cloud Service: Microsoft Azure AZ-900, AI-900, DP-900 Certified, Naver Cloud Platform, AWS, DigitalOcean (and VPS providers)

**DB**: Azure SQL, Azure Cosmos DB, mariaDB, mongoDB, redis

Misc: Linux/UNIX Server (Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS), Git, CloudFlare, React Redux, MUI (React Library), HTML, CSS, Arduino, Raspberry Pi

Language: English (Advanced), Korean (Native)